What do you think?
Birth Time Official Video Program
Virtual!
Photo shoot. I'll do my best!
Don't ever fall off!
Don't ever fall.
It's okay.
Okay.
I see.
He's going down.
Serious throws.
12.4
Oh, that's good. Oh, yeah, that's the feeling.
Nice.
But it was the best.
It was the best. We did it.
We did it.
Even the funny and a little bitter ones...
I'm not being paranoid, I'm having fun, I'm cute, I'm having fun.
No big deal.
I'm a little crazy, but I'm also a little bad at this.
I'm having a lot of fun and it's cute
It's a little more relaxed
I'm a little crazy, but I'm also a little bad at it
Hey...
abs
I have abs.
I have abs
Let your heart beat
We just only want this sound
Ni
Ani
ana
re these blue Patienten
goo
I'm trying my best to climb the tree
Hey cute
Ebibuddy, Dokkun & Hands, the time to grow up
I want life to be so exciting
I want to put a smile on everyone's face
See, there's CANDY for sure
Oh, you're so beautiful.
You're so beautiful.
You've been through a lot, haven't you?
Beautiful, beautiful, beautiful.
It's so white.
I can change the purple.
There's roughness
Live enhance kys me
It's like this.
Are you seeing this?
I'm doing fine.
I'm having fun.
Thanks for watching!
by H.
We are in the final stages of filming. The 1st day of shooting today.
Fun!
One more song for today.
Smoke! Smoke!
Fun!
The first day of shooting for my first solo photo book is over.
I wore a lot of different outfits today.
I've been working hard there now.
It was fun. Enjoy!
Hello everyone. My name is Misato Matsuda.
Today is the second day of the photo book shoot.
I'm sure you've all been intrigued by the images.
How many days have passed?
It's been quite a while.
I had to reskate twice.
So, it's been a while.
So, you can see 22-year-old Misato Matsuda and 23-year-old Misato Matsuda.
It was a good story, but I didn't aim for it.
It turned out to be a good story.
It was a photo shoot for a photo book.
I'm going to be away for a bit on the third day.
I'm excited.
Today, I heard that the shoot is scheduled to end rather early.
I heard that the shoot is going to be finished rather early, so
I'm looking forward to taking pictures.
I'll do my best!
This is an outside shot.
Convenience store style
I'm wearing sandals.
I don't walk around with my stomach out like that in private, so don't worry.
I'm home!
I'm home.
OK.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
♪
AHAHAHAHAHAHA
Money's down.
Go!
Jialin is studying Chinese with Bob and Combination.
Kokoro la la la for your grandfather...
Kokoro la la la la...
La la la la... they showed up.
Lots of birds.Lots of birds
I don't often walk along the Meguro River.
It's refreshing.
I can spend time looking around.
Thank you for watching.
Today, Ms. Misato Matsuda will be in charge of this cake.
Please give her my best regards.
Please give my regards.
More greenery.
Completed
My eyes are so cheap!
From here that clothes Space поэтому
manages to bring
Worms
A little bit
Make it
I think
Sky Watch
I'm getting to the point.
At the time of the competition
I was with
I was indeed a bit of an idiot.
I'm embarrassed
OK, OK, OK
It's over!
We were able to eat such a colorful and sweet cake without any problems!
But you know what?
I had a hard time making the cream
I struggled a lot, but
But thanks to everyone's help, we were able to make it!
It's so delicious, I'm going to eat it all!
Thank you very much!
Good morning.
Thank you very much.
It's the third day of shooting.
We had three days of shooting in different locations.
My shooting is
It's a good time of the year and I'm having a lot of fun.
I think you can see me in different ways.
I think you will be able to see me in many different ways.
Today I am in Izu!
It's so hot in Izu!
It's very humid.
I'll do my best not to sweat as much as possible
Let's go for a run.
Wow!
More stops.
Oh, it's up!
Oh, beautiful.
Oh, I like it. I like your side leg.
I'll never, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever.
I've seen that pose before.
Don't ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever
The sun never shines, what do you think I'm saying?
I'm just yesterday's bedding, yesterday's only
It's like I'm rubbing it back in
Oh, yeah. Tomorrow, too.
Always keep it cool. Be cool.
It's heavy!
It's that time of year again.
I'll be home early.
I gotta go.
Oh, that way?
Hmm?
Not this way? Normal.
Mm-hmm.
Let's play "hide and seek.
You're shaking.
Okay, okay.
Mmm-hmm.
Some for him.
Yay.
Thanks for the help.
Thank you.
Thanks for all your hard work
Thanks for your hard work.
Thanks for your hard work
Welcome back
Welcome home
She's a ray of sunshine.
Rain forecast?
Was it supposed to be cloudy?
It rained this morning.
It cleared up.
It's so bright, it's almost dazzling.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Last photo shoot.
I changed into a pure white dress.
I'm going to the waterfall now.
We're going to the waterfall now.
Is a waterfall really what you think it is?
Is a waterfall really the waterfall you're imagining?
I'm not imagining it at all.
Hang in there with your face.
Hang in there with your face!Good luck with your face.
I'd like to see you over there.
I want to see you over there.
All the time.
I always want to see you there.
I want to see a lot of une
me
It's real!
So close to such a
I don't get to go often
You don't get to see much.
There it is! What a waterfall!
We're looking at the Irila Falls.
Oh, my God! That's amazing! I can see them this close up?
Oh, man!
Wow!
Thank you for watching!
The filming, which took about three days if not one day, has been successfully completed.
Thank you very much.
It was a great experience to be here on such a beautiful negative ion day.
It was a happy summer memory for me, and I hope my mom will be able to see it on the Ding!
I am sure you will watch the channel.
Lads sleigh!
Lots of cheers!
It's true.
It's still pretty fun if you don't get in.
Ooh!
Yum!
It's good!
Is it in?
Yes!
It's in!
Wow!
OK! OK!
OK!
I'm about to say boo.
Is the waterfall really the waterfall you're imagining?
I'm not imagining it at all.
Hmm? I made a mistake.